education.govt.nz 2019-07-23

# Legal and privacy | Education in New Zealand

## Privacy statement

This privacy notice applies to personal and other information collected on this website.

Our privacy policy is governed by the [New Zealand Privacy Act 1993 (external link) ](http://www.legislation.govt.nz/act/public/1993/0028/latest/DLM296639.html "Open external link").

If you voluntarily provide personal information (eg, through email feedback or online forms), we will keep that personal information secure and will not disclose it to any third party. Any personal information supplied will only be used for the purpose for which it was provided or permitted by the Privacy Act 1993 or otherwise required by law.

If you want to check personal information that we hold, or request the correction of that information when required, please either write to:

The Privacy Officer  
Ministry of Education  
PO Box 1666  
Wellington 6140

or email [health.safety.security.privacy@education.govt.nz](mailto:health.safety.security.privacy@education.govt.nz).

For more information on privacy, please visit the [Privacy Commissioner's website (external link) ](http://www.privacy.org.nz/ "Open external link").

## Cookies

Browser cookies are small files that are sent by a website and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies are used by this website to provide the Ministry with information about site usage and to help us improve our website.

Cookies from this site are not used to gather any personally identifiable information. The information we collect includes the date and time you visited the site, your IP address, the pages you accessed on our site, the search terms you used, details about your operating system (eg, Windows 7, Mac OSX) and your web browser (eg, Firefox or Internet Explorer).

The data is collected and aggregated for the Ministry by Google Analytics, a measurement and research service. You can find out about Google Analytics privacy policy in their [Privacy Center (external link) ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "Open external link").

You can manually disable cookies at any time - check your browser's "Help" to find out how. This will not affect your ability to view this site.

## Unsolicited email

Publication of email addresses on this site should not be taken as deemed consent to receiving unsolicited email. Persons or organisations wishing to send email material to individuals or organisations whose email addresses appear on this website must comply with the requirements of the [Unsolicited Electronic Messages Act 2007 (external link) ](http://www.dia.govt.nz/diawebsite.nsf/wpg_URL/Services-Anti-Spam-Index?OpenDocument&ExpandView#three "Open external link").

Last reviewed: 13 November 2018 Has this been useful? [Give us your feedback](http://education.govt.nz/our-work/contact-us/regional-ministry-contacts/your-feedback/)
